<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Movie Reviews</title>
    <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Movie Reviews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es-es</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Guilty</title>
      <link>https://example.com/m/the-guilty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/m/the-guilty/</guid>
      <description>Joe Baylor, an extremely stressed LAPD agent called, is working the night shift at an emergency call center (911), which is filled with calls related to large wildfires in the Hollywood Hills. He has been temporarily suspended from patrol duties and placed on &amp;ldquo;desk duty&amp;rdquo; at the call center, while awaiting a court hearing related to an incident that occurred eight months ago, but is hopeful of returning to normal duties later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Girl</title>
      <link>https://example.com/m/sweet-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/m/sweet-girl/</guid>
      <description>A devastated husband vows to bring justice to the people responsible for his wife’s death while protecting the only family he has left, his daughter.
 Year: 2021 Running time: 96 min. Country: United States Director: Brian Andrew Mendoza Screenwriter: Philip Eisner, Gregg Hurwitz, Will Staples Music: Steven Price Cinematography: Barry Ackroyd Producer: ASAP Entertainment, Pride of Gypsies, On The Roam Distributor: Netflix Cast: Jason Momoa, Isabela Merced, Manuel Garcia-Rulfo, Adria Arjona, Raza Jaffrey, Justin Bartha, Lex Scott Davis, Michael Raymond-James, Dominic Fumusa, Nelson Franklin, Reggie Lee, Bryan Howe, Dale Pavinski  Trailer  Sweet Girl Official Trailer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oxygen</title>
      <link>https://example.com/m/oxygen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/m/oxygen/</guid>
      <description>A woman wakes up in a medical cryogenic unit. She does not remember who she is or how she ended up locked in a box no bigger than a coffin. While running out of oxygen, he must rebuild his memories to escape that nightmare.
 Year: 2021 Running time: 101 min. Country: France Director: Alexandre Aja Screenwriter: Christie LeBlanc Music: Robin Coudert Cinematography: Maxime Alexandre Producer: Co-production France-United States; Echo Lake Productions, Wild Bunch, Getaway Films Distributor: Netflix Cast: Mélanie Laurent, Malik Zidi, Marc Saez, Eric Herson-Macarel, Cathy Cerda  Trailer  Oxygen Official Trailer</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
